This is kind of...
Y'know, it's embarrassing even for me, but...
I really wanna take in what
you're going to say, Rin.
Senpai, I...
Episode 8              Adults
So, there you have it...
Rin's gonna be coming by every
now and then to hang out.
I figured... you should know, Mom.
Th-Thank you for having me!
It's a pleasure to have you around.
You let me know if anything's
bothering you, okay?
R-Right!
No, I mean, nothing bothers me
about Senpai! Ma'am!
Was that a good answer?!
Did I do that right?!
My boy is finally leaving the nest...
Knock it off!
I-If you're worried about that,
I can always move into this nest!
I didn't mean it that way!
Y'know, I always did want a daughter...
Why are you so on board with this?
I didn't mean it that way, though!
I can play the role
of daughter or sister, too!
Because I get a lot of practice
portraying Senpai's harem!
Eiji...?
Were you cleaning up?
Yep.
Getting rid of old books and such.
Mom's gonna chew me out
if I don't get it done.
But she seems so nice.
These... aren't really the kind of
notepads you're supposed to doodle in.
Sensei, it's not what you think.
If you hadn't been able to graduate,
I could've helped you study.
Dammit, I just had to barely
make it over the finish line!
That is a good thing, right...?
This is from our trip to Kyoto.
It's not that funny!
These are all getting put away!
That seems like such a shame!
Are you getting rid of your uniform too?
Yeah. No need to wear it anymore.
I won't get to see you
in that uniform ever again...
Don't say it with that look on your face.
But, y'know...
We could go on dates wearing our uniforms.
Come on, what's the harm?!
Just once!
Would I be interrupting right now?
Oh, no!
What else am I supposed to do?
Please, it can't end like this!
That sounds bad!
You've got a lot of random
toys in here, Senpai.
Yeah, I use it to make props.
Clay! That takes me back.
Feel free to open it.
Rin-san... what the...
Is it a landslide?
I was hoping you'd get it, Senpai.
I don't know if I can spoil you that much!
But calling it a landslide?
My bad, my bad.
So mean...
Crash!
You can have him, Senpai!
Uh... but what is it?
Seriously, what is it?
Make sure to put it on display!
But what exactly is it?!
Um, Senpai, are we...
Maybe a little too childish?
Maybe less "us" and more "you," Rin.
It's both of us!
I want to do something more grown-up.
What, like holding each other?
You seem pretty childish to me, Senpai!
Then it's a race to see
who can grow up first!
You're on!
Go on. Come over here.
Senpai!
Sorry about the delay.
You actually wore the uniform!
It's a little embarrassing, though,
since I'm too grown up for it!
But it suits you perfectly.
Say what?!
Wearing this uniform really reminds me...
Of those days I spent,
giving it my all, every day.
That was just the other day.
It's all coming back so vividly...
It wasn't that long ago!
So cute!
I like the face!
You've got a needlessly
pleasant texture, buddy!
You're acting like
a high school student, Senpai.
I guess I got carried away...
But I'm not some kid who gets giddy
at the sight of a stuffed critter anymore.
"Play with me some more!"
"I'm real fluffy! Feels real good!"
There!
This texture... might be my favorite.
Want me to buy you one
as an enrollment present?
I want a hundred!
Now that is childish!
It's a relief seeing you're
still acting like a kid.
Dang it! I really wanna show
off my adult side, now...
What about paying the adult ticket price?
Oh, Onee-chan!
Aya! Are you on the way home?
Yeah. I was at Moe-chan's house.
Good to see you again, Ayaka-chan.
Hello!
Are you okay?
You're gonna catch a cold
if you don't dress more warmly.
Here you go.
So fluffy...
Isn't that nice?
They're warm and comfy!
Right?
Now, make a fist like this.
And then we bump elbows.
Like this?
You never change, do you, Senpai?
I mean, you treat everyone the same way.
You think so?
You do...
Well,
I think the way you're able to act
differently depending on if you're acting,
or being a kouhai,
or a big sister is more impressive.
I hope you keep being
able to adapt like that.
Into Tsundere-chan
and Imp-chan and the rest...
You laughed at me!
Onee-chan, look!
Well, we can give them back tomorrow.
Aya, can I borrow those?
No.
Pseudo Harem
What kind of adult do you wanna be
when you grow up, Megu?
A sexy one.
Must be nice having such a clear goal...
You must be really out of it.
I gave you a huge opening just now.
You must be desperate
to catch up to Senpai-san, huh?
Yeah...
Well, I think people who have
it together are pretty mature.
Well, if you think about it,
our job is to enjoy this
last year as high-schoolers
instead of trying so hard, right?
Right?!
Wow, what got into you?
Fine, I guess I don't
have it together at all...
I wonder if Senpai's
gonna be okay in college.
I hope he's making friends.
Now you're sounding grown-up.
How?!
By worrying more about
someone other than yourself!
I wonder if that boy will be
able to handle his own meals?
Yeah, no, that's just being his mom.
I wonder how college students dress...
I... have no idea.
You gotta help me make some choices, Rin.
If I choose, I'm just gonna end up
with more wacky t-shirts.
You really want my help?!
I can't wait for Sunday!
Calling Kitahama-Senpai
I wonder who I should
have pick them out for me?
Imp-chan?
I bet Demure-chan would
pick out some mature clothes!
I am not going to be acting!
I bet Spoiled-chan is pretty fashionable...
I said no!
Me! I'm going to choose!
I had to try.
I showed up pretty early.
Was I looking forward to this too much?
We weren't supposed to meet until 10.
I'll contact her later.
Okay, goodnight.
Right. Sleep well.
-Today-
Could we meet up a little early today?
"Nah. I just woke up." There.
Rin?!
Senpai, you liar!
Were you looking forward to seeing me?
Well, you showed up early, too!
Well, I was really excited!
No fair, being honest at a time like this...
I'm glad that you feel the same way, Senpai!
No fair!
Besides, aren't the shops
still closed this early?
This isn't right.
This one...
No, the colors are...
Something more mellow?
And maybe a longer hem...
She keeps muttering to herself...
I tried it on.
You look so grown-up!
What's wrong?
You put so much thought into this choice.
I appreciate it.
It started getting fun, so...
You looked this serious!
I did not!
This one...? Or maybe this one...?
Mutter mutter mutter mutter!
Come on!
Next, I'll pick something out for you, Rin.
Could you look a little less hostile?
Ladies first!
Fank yoo so much!
What kind of voice is that?
It's my voice for the kitties!
Cat Cafe
Yeah, but they're not actually here yet!
Come here, sweetie...
Senpai! Look!
What? You called?
What the—?!
So nice...
Must be nice...
They love me!
I don't have enough hands to pet them all!
That's fine.
I'm just gonna play with this one.
I'm a one-cat girl, you know.
Meow.
Meow...
Meow, meow meow meow.
What exactly are you doing, Cool-chan?
Are you friends already?
This one responds to you!
Yeah, but mine climb all over me.
They've turned you
into a cat tower, though.
You mean I'm just a toy to them?
Man, now I'm starting to feel jealous.
Do you mind if our party joins you?
But we were having a quiet, intimate moment!
Oh, no!
Sharing is caring!
Want me to walk you home?
Just to the bus station is fine.
But we won't see each other
again until next week...
I don't want to ask for too much.
Rin.
Senpai?
Just let me recharge.
Now I should be fine until I see you again.
Don't forget about me
for even a single day, okay?
All right. When I get home, I'm gonna
plaster your pics all over my room!
You're leaving already? Walk me home!
Okay, now you're being spoiled!
Headed your way
Wait for me by the front gate
Understood!
Oh, Senpai...
Rin!
Senpai? What's wrong?
Look... I don't know
how to tell you this, but...
But a classmate of mine
asked me out at college today.
I turned her down, of course,
but then she cried a ton...
And now I'm feeling down too.
Um...
I don't know what to say.
If you don't know, then I guess
it's only natural that I wouldn't!
What a relief! Now I feel a little better.
Come to think of it, the outfit
you chose for me was a hit.
Everyone said I look great!
That's never happened before!
Is Senpai popular at college?!
Meow meow meow meow!
Much Ado About Nothing
I never thought we'd get married.
I thought for sure when you became
an actress you'd land some hot actor...
And after you moved to Hollywood?
Don't get me started!
I've seriously moved up in the world!
I never forgot about you, even once.
Rin...!
Then again, as an art director of renown,
we have worked together
in world-class projects around the globe!
This is a lot of new
background information...